Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Physics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Physics, records
1905-1994
1960-1994
SC0952
Stanford University. Department of Physics.
60 Linear feet
Collection includes minutes of faculty meetings (1905-1948), administrative files, budget and financial records, grant files, technical reports, correspondence, and other materials. Some of the files are from the period when Walter Meyerhoff was chair of the department but other chairmen are also represented in the records. Also of note are files pertaining to the recruitment of minority students and women students and files on the Mexican-American Program: Stanford Summer Program of Mexican-American High School Students (mid-1960s).
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Collection includes minutes of faculty meetings (1905-1948), administrative files, budget and financial records, grant files, technical reports, correspondence, and other materials. Some of the files are from the period when Walter Meyerhoff was chair of the department but other chairmen are also represented in the records. Also of note are files pertaining to the recruitment of minority students and women students and files on the Mexican-American Program: Stanford Summer Program of Mexican-American High School Students (mid-1960s).
Access Terms
Meyerhof, Walter E. (Walter Ernst), 1922-; Stanford University. Department of Physics. Faculty.; Stanford University. Department of Physics.; Walecka, John Dirk, 1932-; Mexican American students.; Minority college students; Physics--Study and teaching.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1997-092
  - American Physical Society Meeting, Stanford University 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Physical Society 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Institute of Physics (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Professors 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accident Reports - General 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic Senate 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Applied Physics Division 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Appointment Policy 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Procedures 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - University Archives 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biophysics Laboratory 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Black Students Study At Stanford 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Civil Defense 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coffee Party - Physics Grads 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Commencement 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commission Of College Physics 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committee Assignments 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Examination 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Computer Facilities 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Conferences at Stanford 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Course Enrollments 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Course Listings 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Course Review 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Courses amp;amp;amp; Degrees 1962-1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Convocations - Freshman 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Curriculum Discussions 1959-1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Employment Seeking – General 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Examination Schedules 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Absences from Campus 1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Absence Forms 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Leave Policy Procedures amp;amp;amp; Forms 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Salaries – General 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Fellowship Program 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Visitors 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Foreigners - Visa amp;amp;amp; Tax Information 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Seminar Program 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fund Raising (Including PACE) 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Future Plans amp;amp;amp; Policies 1948-1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - General Studies Program Bulletin 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Gifts - Anonymous amp;amp;amp; General 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Division, Stanford University 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Office, Physics Department 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hansen Labs – General 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Health Service - General 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Housing 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Humanities amp;amp;amp; Sciences Faculty Body 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Services Committee 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meetings 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Committee Meetings 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Study Committee 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Advisors Committee 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Education Study, Stanford University 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Selective Service Committee 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Research Facilities Committee 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Radiation Committee 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Library Committee 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Study Committee 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Physics Club 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Advisors Committee 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Admission amp;amp;amp; Awards Committee 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - General Studies amp;amp;amp; Advisors 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Special Consultant Committee 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Advisors Committee 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Students Advisor 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Colloquium Committee 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Committee 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Multilithograph Records 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Schiff Memorial Contributors Acknowledgment Letters I-Q, S-Z 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Humanities amp;amp;amp; Sciences - General 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Housing, Inventory, Miscellaneous 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Indirect Cost (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Inquiries, Miscellaneous 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - International Center 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Klystron Royalties 1952-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Library 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Lists: Faculty, Research Associates, Staff, Visitors 1961-1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - M General 1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - MAP (Mexican-American Program: Stanford Summer Program of Mexican-American High School Students) 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Minority Programs 1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Cap amp;amp;amp; gown 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Military Deferments – Procedure 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Moving Expenses – Procedure 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Names amp;amp;amp; Addresses 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NSF (National Science Foundation) 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - National Service 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - News Releases (including Sit-Ins) 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Other Departments – General 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Parties - All Functions 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Pass-Fail Grading 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Patent Policies 1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Personnel Information from Encina 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - PhD Degrees – Physics 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Physics 58 “New Laboratory” 1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - “Physics amp;amp;amp; Man” Lecture Series 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Physics Department Miscellaneous 1956-1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Physics Lecture Hall 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Placement Services 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Police 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Postdoctoral Awards 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Posters amp;amp;amp; Circulars (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Printing Schedules 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - President’s Reports 1946-1963 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - President’s Reports 1963-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Professors Correspondence 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaire Department 1 Information 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Radiological Hazards Control Committee 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Registrar 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Research Administration Office (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Russian Visitors 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - S General 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Safety Office 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Schawlow Open House 1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Secretarial Group 1964 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Secretaries Information 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Sigma Xi Society 1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - SLAC Coordinating Committee 1966 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - SLAC – General 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Sloan Foundation Fellowships, etc. 1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - SPIRES (Stanford Physics Information Retrieval System) 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Staff 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Stipends 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Student, Summer Employment Requests 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Student Petitions 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Summer Salaries 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - T General 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Teaching Assignments 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Teaching amp;amp; Research Assistance – General 1961-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Text Book Lists 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Travel Funds – Departmental 1956-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Overseas Campuses 1967 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - University Administration 1962-1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Varian Building II 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Visitors, Guests, Research Associates Policy 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Visitors – Inquiries amp;amp; By-Day 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Visitors to Other Departments 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship 1967 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - MAP 1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Minority Admissions Advisory Committee 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - NSF 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Natural Sciences 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - O General 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Observatory 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - P General 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - President’s Reports 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Privacy 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Research Development Fund 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Research Development Fund Exhibition 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Research Development Fund Information- Provost Proposal 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - S General 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Safety Office 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Schiff Memorial Correspondence 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Schiff Memorial Fund Letters 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sponsored Projects Office 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Stipends 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Student Correspondence 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Student Petitions: 290, etc. 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Student Employment 1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Study of Graduate Education at Stanford University 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Summer Session Program 1955-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Task Force Committee 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Assignments 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Teaching amp;amp; Research Assistants – General 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Travel Funds- Departmental 1970-1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - U General (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Studies 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Costs 2/1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Computer Service 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Draft Information 1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Fellowships 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Studies 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Grant Foundation 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Minority Admissions 1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Personnel Memoranda 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Physics Majors 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Physics Papers 1971 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Purchasing Department Memoranda 1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Research Administrations Memoranda (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Safety amp;amp; Health (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - SLAC (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Teaching Assistants (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Tuition Grants (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - United Fund (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Meeting Minutes, Staff Records, etc. 1945-1955 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Meeting Minutes, Staff Records, etc. 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Meeting Minutes, Staff Records, etc. 1953-1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Textbooks 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Varian Building General Design 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Varian Building General Information 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Financial Journal 1920-1924 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Experiments in Elementary Physics, Hansen amp;amp; Richtmyer 1936 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Grant Proposal: NSF PH73-08920 Renewal 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Energy Management 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Employee Recruitment amp;amp; Selection Manual 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ritson “Development of Reflecting Optics” Proposals, etc. 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Lebedev Notes, Equations, Graphs 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Grant Proposal: NSF PMR80-26007 1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Grant Proposal: NSF CSSA 4-84 1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Grant Proposal: NASA CSSA 4-84 1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Wojcicki, Alan - Chairman Chronological File 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Walecka, J. Dirk - Chairman Chronological File 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Fetter, A.L. - Center For Materials Research Seed Proposals, Thrust Budgets, Awards 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Varian Building I 1959-1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Varian Building Renovations 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Varian Building Mailboxes 1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Varian Building Paging System 1966 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Varian Building Telephone Codes 1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Varian Building Diagrams 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - American Physical Society Meeting, Stanford University 12/1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New Building Committee Meeting Minutes 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - MAP 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - MAP Student Participation surveys (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - MAP Material 1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - MAP Physics Today article 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - MAP 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Technical Reports: Spectroscopy amp; Quantum Electronics Group 1972-1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Technical Reports: Spectroscopy amp; Quantum Electronics Group 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Varian building Design amp; Construction 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Sloan Accounts 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Budget Sheets 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Budget Sheets 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Budget 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Budget 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Budget 1950-1955 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Budget 1855-1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Budget 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1948-1950 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1950-1955 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1955-1957 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1957-1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Faculty amp; Departmental Memoranda 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Varian Building Activation Budget 1963 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Varian Building Activation Budget Statement 1964 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Varian Building Construction (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Varian Building Ind. Change Orders (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Varian Building Architect Correspondence 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Varian Building Basement Extension 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - NSF Grant Information 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Advanced Laser Source Research: Financial Records ONR N0014-78-C-0403 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Advanced Laser Source Research: ONR Proposal 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Advanced Laser Source Research: ONR Proposals amp; Award 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records: Budget, Approvals, Requisitions, Correspondence 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records: 2FEQ705-706, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records: 1-FEL-401; 2-FEL-411; 2-FEL-602; 2-FES-402; 2-FEW-401 1975-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEL-902 (Little) 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEL-722 (Little) 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records: 1-FEH-702 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records: 1-FEH-703 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Grant Proposal: Schawlow “Near Zero” Sloan 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Grant Proposal: Fairbank NSF 1978-1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Contract: Fairbank, DeBra, Taber “Functional Charge” AFOSR (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEF-606 1975-1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEF-457 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEV-402 1982-1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEV-437 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEV-438 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEV-439 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Advanced Laser Source Research: Schawlow Report Draft ONR 1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Grant Proposal: Susskind “Elemental Particle Physics” NSF 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Superconductivity” NASA 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Superconductivity” NASA 1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Sensing of Molecules” 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEL-413 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEL-150 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEL-901 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Financial Records: 2-FEL-414 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Superconductivity” NASA 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Microminiature… “ ONR 1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Organic Conductors… ” NASA 1977 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Sensing of Molecules” NSF 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Development of Structure” ONR 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Assay of Proteins” HE amp;W 1977-1981 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Thin Film… “ Caltech 1974 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Computer-Assisted Instruction” 1972 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Development of Design… “ 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Assay of Proteins” HE&W 1976-1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Organic Conductors” NSF 1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Textbooks 1951-1960 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Textbooks 1961-1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1905-1923 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1923-1926 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1923-1926 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1927-1930 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1930-1933 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - School Of Physical Sciences Meeting Minutes 1926-1933 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1932-1934 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1933-1940 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1940-1943 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1935-1941 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1941-1943 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1945-1947 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Department Meeting Minutes 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Study Committee Minutes 1947-48 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Readers 1945-1947 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Former Faculty 1945-1947 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Memoranda 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Departmental Parties 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Personnel Memoranda 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Benefits TIAA-CREF Retirement Fund 1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - University Committee on Minority Affairs 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Evaluation Committee Memoranda, Reports 1979-1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Post Graduation Questionnaires 1986-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Curriculum & Teaching Evaluation 1984-1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Minority Recruitment Grants 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - MAP 1965 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - MAP Evaluations 1965 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - MAP Physics Minority Group (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - MAP Mailing Lists 1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - MAP Proposal (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - MAP East Side Union High School Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - MAP Martin Tucker Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - MAP Rosenberg Foundation Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - MAP Potential Help (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - MAP Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - MAP Stanford University Committee (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - MAP Sally’s Abraham Lincoln High School Yearbook 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - MAP Application Tests 1966 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - MAP 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - MAP Student Applications A-Y 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - MAP Alternatives 1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - MAP Acceptance Letters (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - MAP MAYO (Mexican-American Youth Organization) Conference 12/4/1965 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - MAP Applications 1966 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - MAP Miscellaneous Correspondence 1966 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - MAP NSF Proposal (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - MAP East Side Union High School 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - MAP William Sommerville, UC Berkeley 1966 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - MAP Upward Bound 1966 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - MAP Literature (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - MAP Students & Direct Letters 1965 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - MAP Admissions 1965 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - MAP Measurement (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - MAP Libraries (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - MAP Transport (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - MAP Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - MAP Committee Notes & Memoranda 1966 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - MAP Schedule 1966 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - MAP Incentive Scholarships 1965 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - MAP General 1966 (Box 29, Folder 16)